Guide to the Chase Kimball Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1900s-1970s, undated; Accession 1990-M-063; 9.5 linear feet (10 boxes)
  - Second Congregational Society, Waterbury
    - Committee minutes and budget, 1930s-1940s (Box 4)
    - Legal matters, 1930s-1940s (Box 4)
    - Endowments, 1930s (Box 4)
  - General Council of the Congregational and Christian Churches of the U.S. (3 folders), 1930s-1940s (Box 4)
  - Council for Social Action (CSA) of the Congregational Christian Churches of the U.S. (2 folders), 1930s-1940s (Box 4)
  - Waterbury Council of Churches (3 folders), 1930s-1940s, undated (Box 4)
  - Cooperative for American Remittances to Europe, Inc.(CARE), 1940s (Box 4)
  - Corporations, printed material, and annual reports, 1940s-1970s (Box 4)
  - Encyclopedia of Relevant Knowledge, 1950s-1960s (Box 5)
  - Entertainment programs, 1900s-1940s,1960s, undated (Box 5)
  - Institute of International Education, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
  - Institute of Politics, "Report of the Round Tables and General Conference at the Sixth Session", 1926 (Box 5)
  - International Court of Justice of the United Nations, 1945, undated (Box 5)
  - International relations, undated (Box 5)
  - International University conferences, 1953-1954 (Box 5)
  - Italo-Ethiopian controversy, 1935-1936 (Box 5)
  - "Journeys Behind the News," radio broadcast transcripts (7 folders), 1947-1950 (Box 5)
  - Ludlow war referendum, 1937-1939, undated (Box 5)
  - Memorabilia (4 folders), 1930s-1940s undated (Box 5)
  - National Association of Foreign Student Advisers (NAFSA), 1948-1949, undated (Box 5)
  - National Peace Conference, 1945 April 25-June 10 (Box 5)
  - Neutrality legislation, 1937-1939 (Box 5)
  - New College, Sarasota, Florida, 1960s, undated (Box 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1920s, 1940s, undated (Box 6)
  - Notes, undated (Box 6)
  - Peace organizations (3 folders), 1940s-1950s, undated (Box 6)
  - Peace work - churches, 1930s (Box 6)
  - Photographs, 1943-1948, undated (Box 6)
  - Pine Mountain Settlement School, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Political issues, material pertaining to (6 folders), 1920s-1940s, undated (Box 6)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 6)
  - Professional employment possibilities (Box 6)
  - Sanctions against Italy, 1935-1936 (Box 6)
  - School compositions, workbooks, 1900s-1920s, undated (Box 6)
  - Sherwood Eddy American seminar (2 folders), 1934 (Box 6)
  - Social Action, 1935-1937 (Box 7)
  - Speech excerpt, 1938 January 30 (Box 7)
  - Speeches, notes, 1930s, undated (Box 7)
  - Suffolk University (3 folders), 1960s-1970s (Box 7)
  - Taft School, 1917-1922, 1936 (Box 7)
  - United Nations, background material, 1940s-1950s (Box 7)
  - United Nations Association of Greater Boston (UNAGB) (4 folders), 1960s-1970s (Box 7)
  - United States Congress, 1960s-1970s (Box 7)
  - U.S. Constitution, Bricker proposal, 1950s (Box 7)
  - Vietnam War and American oil interests, 1971, undated (Box 7)
  - World War I, causes, cost, method, 1915-1930s (Box 7)
  - World War II, causes, cost, method (3 folders), 1930s-1952, undated (Box 7)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, "Europe in Summer of 1938", 1938 June 22-September 4 (Box 7)
  - Berea College, 1928-1965 (Box 8)
  - Berea College, 1966-1971 (Box 9)
  - Berea College, 1972-1974, undated (Box 10)